Quite an exciting step for us to know that you can do interactive stuff but still
インタラクティブな事ができると知る事は、僕らにとって、とてもエキサイティングなステップだ。
have a style to it, and an aesthetic to it, that we're more comfortable with as well.
だけどそこに、あるスタイルと美的な価値観を持ってね。そうなると、さらに満足度が高くもなる。
I think we've hit on the starting point of the technology that meets our aesthetics
僕らは僕らの美的感覚を満たすテクノロジーを使い始めていると思う。
and then the next step is to push the storytelling side of it more
そして次のステップはストーリーを伝える部分を強くしていく事だと思う。
I think that it'll be nice to start kind of coming back to the characters
僕は、キャラクターを使うところにもどってみるのが良いんじゃないかと思ってる。
cause really that I think where we, what we enjoy is the people side of things
なぜなら、僕らが楽しんでいるのは物事の人間的な側面だからだ。
it's why I do more documentary stuff as well, and music video based stuff but
だから、僕はドキュメンタリーとか、ミュージックビデオをベースとした物を、パフォーマンス的にやっている。
performative, to bring the characters back into it now, we've established the look
それはキャラクターを今、再度そこで使うためなんだ。僕らはその見た目と、
and the interactive aspect of it.
インタラクティブな側面を確立してきた。
One of the nicest, rounded facts that we came across was this first
僕らが出会った、もっとも良く完成された事実の一つは、この始めての
broadcast that came out of Traffic Park in the 20s, so it's literally, probably a stones,
交通公園から発信された20世紀の放送だ。それは文字通りここから目と鼻の先、
probably about a hundred miles from where you are now
今いる場所、から大体100マイル先にある。
in sort of an industrial factories area was where this original set up was.
そこは工業工場地帯で、元々その施設の合った場所だ。
It was just basically a tented structure that they broadcast from.
彼らが放送をしている所は、基本的にテントのような構造をしていた。
And they had to devise their own microphone to be able to play back singing
彼らは歌を再生できるようにするために、自分たち自身のマイクを創り出さなくてはならなかった。
because the other microphones would just distort and it was called a "photophone"
なぜなら、他のマイクでは、音が歪んでしまうからで、そのマイクはフォトフォンと呼ばれていた。
they used a series of seven steps that, basically they converted sound into light
彼らは7ステップのシリーズ回路を使って、基本的に音を光に変換した。
and back into sound again and then back
そして、再び音に戻したのだ。そして、
A full precursor to anything fiberoptic that's all going on now.
現代使用されている光ファイバーの完全な先駆けだった。
The history is quite appealing for us, I think. I tend to fall back into the idea of digging
歴史はとても魅力的だと思う。僕はキットのような物を深く調べるというアイデアに立ち戻る事がある。
into some of the kit, in terms of sort of a media archeology, and hopefully
メディア考古学というか、願わくば、
start using some of their kit that was used in the 40s, 50s, 60s
そういった例えば40年代、50年代、60年代に使われていたキットを使って、
and look at what can be done in terms of twisting that in new ways
それを新しい使い方で使ったときに、それで何が出来るのかを見るんだ。
some of the cameras, and microphones, and things like that.
ある種のカメラやマイクなどの物を使ってね。
So in a cheap way I can shoot on video and then reproject back to film to get
だからずるい方法だけど、ビデオに撮って、そのあとそれをフィルムに写しなおして、
the loops and break it down into parts and it becomes it's own aesthetic just
ループを作り、パーツごとに分解する。そしたらなんでもそのプロセスを通すことで、それ自身の美しさが出てくるんだ。
through that process anyway. It's got this glow and this sheen that doesn't feel like
そのプロセスでこの輝きと、艶を得る。その感じは
it's been shot straight on film, it doesn't look like video at all.
フィルムに直で撮ったショットのようにはならないし、その質感はビデオで撮った映像とも異なる。
We developed quite a lot of our own film stock as well. We get really nice effects where
僕らは沢山の自分たちの独自のフィルムストックも開発した。それで本当に良いエフェクトが手に入るんだ。使うには
we just literally use the container to wind the film through, then you have to hang it up
僕らが文字通りその入れ物を使ってフィルムを曲げ、それからお風呂に吊るさないといけないんだ。
in your bathroom to dry and you get all the details and the blobs on it that gives you the
乾かすために。ここでどんな風な絵になったかが分かる。絵の上に斑点が出来てて、それは、
hand dev in black and white film that's synchronized, something like the Kinect
手の深みを白黒のフィルムの上で伝えてくれる。それは同期しているんだ。キネクトの様にね。
you get some lovely results with this. 	Really nice stuff.
それですごくラブリーな結果を得る事が出来るんだ。本当に良い物なんだよ。